[Music] BLUEY THEME TUNE
Chilling on the couch, reading about the Prime Minister.
Oh, what's he done now?
Dad, can you play a song on your phone for us?
Ah... yeah, OK. As long as it's not too annoying.
No, it's not annoying.
What's it called?
Burger dog!
Burger dog.
OK. There you go.
# Burger Dog
# B-Burger Dog
# He has pickles
# And he has cheese
# Burger Dog
# B-Burger Dog
# Fluffy bun with some sesame seeds
# Burger Dog
# B-Burger Dog
# Yap-yap-yap-yap-yap-yap-yap
# Burger Dog
# B-Burger Dog
# He was a weiner, but now he’s a Burger Dog
# Burger Dog, B-Burger Dog #
Hey!
Ah, sorry, kids – my phone's ran out of battery.
No, it hasn't!
Show us!
Hey!
[Bluey] You’re tricking us!
[Bingo] Argh!
[Bluey] Just because the screen is black...
- Get off me!
- ...doesn’t mean it's out of battery!
- Bluey!
I know!
Look, I really want to listen to Hamburger Dog too,
it's a hauntingly beautiful song.
But, you know, these new phones,
when you update the software, it stops your battery.
You know, they're trying to make you get the flash new one.
- (Groans)
But I'm not having it!
- Rrr-rrr!
Rrr!
- It's out of battery, kid.
Trust me, I would never lie to you.
(PHONE RINGS)
Hello?
Are you lying to your children again?
[Bluey and Bingo] Yes.
[Music] BLUEY THEME TUNE
- Huh!
- (GIGGLES)
All right. A brand new Bingo 3000.
Come and check it out.
Just pop these down.
- Boop!
Hey, what?
Boop!
Well, that's not right.
There we go.
- Boop!
Hey!
Oh, man. This thing's busted.
- (GIGGLES)
- Must be a number on here somewhere.
Here we go.
3-3-3-4-4-4-5-3-3.
Typical.
(GIGGLES)
Technical support.
Boop!
Er, yeah, hello? Yes, I'm fine, yeah.
Look, I just bought a Bingo 3000.
I'm having some problem with the bottom kind of legs bit.
Yeah, you straighten them out and they just go back up.
- Boop!
Yeah, I tried that. Doesn't work.
Oh, OK. Yeah, I'll try that.
So grab this bit, yeah? Now what?
- (GIGGLES)
Just jiggle it? OK. Jiggle, jiggle, jiggle!
Gnnnnn! OK, I’ve jiggled it.
Just try this again.
- Boop!
- Nah, didn't work, mate.
What else you got?
Yeah, OK. I'm looking underneath.
Just poke around? OK, can do.
- (SQUEALS)
Boop!
Nah, mate – didn’t work. Still busted.
Now what? Poke the front bit? OK.
- (SQUEALS)
Boop!
Nah. Look, mate, I want my money back.
What?
Mate, I'm not driving all the way back into you guys, all right?
I’ve got finals footy this arv...
You guys come pick it up.
I don’t know, send a taxi!
What do you mean, you're not going to do that?
Ah, forget you!
That's it! Grrr!
- (SQUEALS)
(GASPS)
It worked! It worked!
- Boop!
Argh!
Bingo 3000? Magazine.
Boop... boop... boop...
- Hmm. I thought this thing would be faster.
- ..boop... boop... boop...
Don't get me started.
[Music] BLUEY THEME TUNE
[Music] BURGER DOG
[Muffin’s Dad, off-screen] OK... go.
Hi everybody, I’m Muffin.
Welcome to my unboxing video.
Er, Dad... I have to go to the toilet.
[Muffin’s Dad] Muffin! (BEEP)
Hi, welcome to my unboxing video.
Today we're going to open this dump truck.
(PING)
Dad, I don't want a Dump Truck.
I want Cat Squad Kitty Island.
[Muffin’s Dad] Muffin, this is the one they sent us, OK?
Just say the line.
But I want Cat Squad Kitty Island! (BEEP)
OK, so, I open this bit.
Eh. Eh...  EHH!
It's stuck! EEE!
Aaagh! Yagh! Agh!
[Muffin’s Dad] Don’t break it, Muffin!
Agh, come on! Yagh! Agh!
[Muffin] I told you.
- Agh!
Agh... you’ve really done a number on this thing. (BEEP)
This is a dump truck.
[Muffin’s Dad] Push the button.
(SIGHS) You push this button, and it does this.
[Muffin’s Dad] Push it harder.
It's not working!
[Muffin’s Dad] Push it properly.
I am! (BEEP)
You have to remember to put batteries in it first.
[Muffin’s Dad] Oh, thank f... (BEEP)
Oh, that's pretty cool. (BEEP)
Maybe I should put some rocks in the back.
(LOUDLY EATS SWEETS)
Hey! (CARRIES ON EATING LOUDLY) Agh!
- No! That’s for the video! Gimme those! (BEEP)
This is a dump truck.
It is the worst toy ever.
I hate it.
[Socks] Can I have it?
No! It's mine!
[Music] BURGER DOG
[Music] BLUEY THEME TUNE
Look at this, girls.
[Together] What is it?
- It's a letter!
It was written by your daddy for school
when he was just a little boy.
[Together] Ooh!
- I've saved it all these years.
Would you like me to read it?
[Together] Yes, please!
OK, here we go.
“My name is Bandit Heller.”
Oh, he spelled Healer wrong.
[Together] (GIGGLE)
“I am fiv years old.”
I think he means five years old.
[Together] (GIGGLE)
Your daddy wasn't a very good speller, was he?
“For my bathday, my mom bogort me a skatboard.”
- [Together] (GIGGLE)
- “The clower of my skatboard is... gren”?
I think he means the colour of his skateboard was green.
“I ride my skatboard on the drivway after skol.”
Oh, Bandy, that's not even close to how you spell school.
“I have a brid.”
A “brid”? What’s he on about?
“My brid's nam is Conan.”
Oh, he's talking about his bird.
[Together] (GIGGLE)
- “I fed Conan everyeye day.”
“His winks are gren and blooo and his bek is yillow.”
Well... I think his wings are green and blue
and his beak is yellow. Or his back.
[Together] (GIGGLE)
- “My browther is keld Rad.”
“My otter browther is keld Strip.”
“Strip is good and so is Rad,
but Rad is good too.” What’s he on about?
“My Dad is good, but he shorts at Rad when Rad plays fotty.”
[Together] (GIGGLE)
- Oh, he shouts at Rad when Rad plays footy.
Oh yeah, he did.
[Together] (GIGGLE)
“I loave my mum.”
[All three, together] Aww...
“She is the bast mum in the wahol worl.”
“But I don lick the food she corks.”
“It tasts disgarsting.”
“Especkialy her lazarniya.”
“It is lak etting vommm-it.”
What? Oooh...
[Together] (SQUEAL)
“The end.”
Oh, Bandy.
I'm back!
[Together] (SQUEAL)
You staying for dinner, Bandy?
I'm making my lasaaaa-gna.
Oh, great.
[Music] BLUEY THEME TUNE
Oh, man. I'm starving.
I need to eat something.
- Ah, no. Bandit.
What, am I not allowed to eat food if I'm hungry?
What kind of a regime is this?
- (Sighs) Carry on.
- I could go some chicken bucket.
Oh, I don't want to get in the car, though. Too much traffic.
That'll take ages.
I'm hungry now.
I'm just going to eat one of the kids.
- Agh!
You know the kids don't agree with you.
Ah, she'll be right. I'll have a peppermint tea after.
Put a bit of salt on first. Chew, chew, chew. Swallow.
Oh, man, that was good.
Kids really fill you up.
Was that so bad, Mum?
I'm just saying, the last time you ate a kid,
you were up all night.
It's all good. Oh, hang on.
Ugh. Oh, man.
Something's not sitting right.
- See?
- He-he! Hi!
- Ah, Bingo.
I'm not feeling so good.
It might have been something I ate...
Might have been?
Oh, man, guts are crook.
(MAKES VOMITING NOISE)
Ah, sorry, Bingo.
I didn't mean to chunder on you.
- That's OK.
- Urgh.
(BURPS)
- Are you finished?
- Yep.
- Good.
I hope you've learned your lesson.
Oh, man. Still a bit hungry. (SNIFFS)
Mm. Smells OK... Hoo-argh!
(SQUEALING)
- Ah, Bandit, no!
[Music] BLUEY THEME TUNE
(GIGGLING)
Can we have a story, Dad?
OK. How about the three little pigs?
[Together] Yeah!
- Can you make it funny?
OK. One day, there were these three little pigs called Jingo,
Gruey and, er... Jimmy or something.
But Jimmy was on a team building course for work,
so we won't see him much.
So the first pig, Jingo, built her house out of straw.
And one day, the Big Bad Wolf rocks up
and says, “Little pig, little pig, let me in.”
But Jingo says, “No way, mate. I’m making nachos.”
So the wolf’s like,
“Ah, I just want to talk to you about your electricity provider.”
Jingo’s like, “Oh, that sounds good,”
and she's about to open the door and then she remembers –
“Hang on! I've got solar! Jog on, chief.”
So the Big Bad Wolf huffed and puffed and blew the house in.
- Dad...
(WHISPERS)
- So Jingo called the police, and the police came,
and the little pig, Jingo, was cacking herself
and filming it all on her phone
and posting it on the ‘Gram
and getting heaps of new followers
And the wolf’s all like,
“I didn't do nothing!”
but the cops aren’t buying all that and they’re like,
“You got three priors, mate,
and that Monaro’s stolen, so tell it to the judge, buddy.”
So they put the wolf in jail.
Then the other pig, Gruey,
came and helped rebuild Jingo's house.
but this time, she used Besser blocks.
- Dad, wait!
- Ah, yep.
- (WHISPERS)
And they built a rad pool shaped like an ice cream cone
and filled it with lemonade. Wow. Good idea.
Meanwhile, the Big Bad Wolf scored a softy judge
and was out of jail on good behaviour.
But the judge said, “You gotta go say sorry to those pigs,
or you're back in here, buddy.”
So the wolf walked round to Jingo’s new joint
and Jingo and Gruey said, “Yeah, mate, it’s all cool.
Just don't try and eat us.”
And the wolf's like,
“Yeah, fair enough. I'm going vegan anyway. I just did tofu.”
So they invited him in for a swim to try and make friends,
but he kept peeing in the pool!
[Together] Eeuuww!
So the pigs were like, “Stop peeing in our pool, mate!
It’s lemonade and we're trying to drink it!”
But really, even if it wasn't lemonade,
you shouldn't do it anyway.
It's full of nitrates
and now we're going to have to put heaps of algicide in.
But the Big Bad Wolf kept saying,
“Look, I didn’t pee in the pool!”
And the pigs are like,
“Yeah, you did,” and he’s like,
“Nah-ah, I don't do that sort of thing.
It's against my religion.”
So the next day, they put the stuff in the pool
that makes lemonade turn purple if you pee in it.
They didn't tell this to the Big Bad Wolf.
And he’s there swimming, eating some couscous,
talking about the Broncos.
Then he goes all quiet and stares into space for a second
with this sort of faraway look in his eyes.
And the kids are like, “Here we go... ”
And suddenly the lemonade turns purple around him
and the pigs are like,
“Ah, see! You’re a grub!”
So the wolf was really embarrassed and he ran out crying
and they never saw him again.
But apparently, he went on to become
quite a successful tennis player.
So, you know, the system works.
The end.
[Together] Again!
- No.
[Music] BLUEY THEME TUNE
One day, there was a lovely big field
with grass blowing gently in the breeze. (BLOWS)
- (GIGGLES)
When along came... an antelope!
Doing, doing, doing! Doing-doing-doing!
But the antelope was chased away by a... cheetah!
Purr! Purr! Purr! Purr!
Then the cheetah got tired
and along came some tiny little ants.
(MEUW NOISE)
- (GIGGLES)
But then came an elephant.
Boom-ba-ba, boom-ba-ba, boom-ba-ba, boom!
The elephant left. Phew!
And along came a spider.
- (SQUEALS)
Go away, spider!
No more creepy animals, thanks.
- Phew.
- Oh, wait, here's a snake! Sssss!
- Aaaah!
Frog! Ribbit.
- (LAUGHS)
Ribbit.
Ah, the frog’s gone and along comes a pussycat.
Oh, no!
Oh, no, Bingo. This cat wants to have a nap.
She uses her claws to make a nice bed!
Miaow! Miaow! Miaow! Miaow!
- (SQUEALS)
Ah, the cat’s asleep.
All is well.
- Ahh...
Dinosaur! Roar!
[Music] BLUEY THEME TUNE