Alrighty now, Chris, man.
You and Rihanna, are y'all back together?
No.
And that's just quick.
Quick answer.
But y'all, are you guys cordial?
Yeah, absolutely.
Is the media saying too much or are we saying too little?
Yeah, I think what it is is like, you know, with me, as I did before, you know, I'm not uncomfortable you know, talking about it.
That's why I don't, I didn't give Tina the side I like.
Right, right.
You see, he asked the question.
Yeah, I was gonna put a wall between you.
And with that is just me being just honest with myself, you know me and her have history and me and her are definitely always gonna be
Is it hard to work on your and Rihanna's friendship with so many eyes and ears around or do y'all know how to just kinda zone in?
Your situation anymore, you know, I think everybody feels so attached to this this old situation I mean, it's still a very detrimental situation because it's stuff that we deal with today And that's why I'm doing like the Genesee Center and all this other stuff that shows the domestic violence That is that is not okay.
But as far as like our personal life I think people just got to give it a chance like give and not even give it a chance shut the hell up
That's basically what it is.
It's me.
At the end of the day, whatever opinion they have ain't going to change nothing I'm doing.
It hasn't and it ain't going to change nothing they're doing.
They're the fans, sit back and watch.
That's all you're doing anyway.
That's what they got to do.
Do you guys
I was just hanging out.
You can get some chips or something.
It was like, oh, they got pictures of us.
Look what we got on.
We fly.
It was some young stuff.
So now as I'm getting older and more mature, it's not as relevant because that's not what makes me an artist and that's not what sustains my longevity.
You know, I think I'm just you know, I think my talent speaks for itself So I think as far as the personal life, you know, it's just whatever it pans out I'm just living life.
However, it falls into place.
It's gonna fall into place I'm not trying to you know, rush anything put any rings on anybody's fingers or lie to anybody I just I just rather be completely honest express my feeling the video that you put out Yeah, what was the what was the reason?
What was Chris Brown thinking?
Okay, I'm gonna put this video out be in love with 2 because you know what it is.
I know
God definitely gives, doesn't put, doesn't give us too much to handle, you know, that we can't handle.
But I also know that he put me in a position, not just say, because I don't know my full purpose.
I can't just say, Chris, I do music, this is what I'm here to do.
I don't know
I feel it's good to share with people because it's an experience and it's a learning and a life lesson.
And there's probably thousands of young teenagers who are going through this, not saying they got money, they flashy or whatever the case, but they could be young playboys or young whatever the case and they don't know how to deal with a situation and they're hurting people in the process or they're, oh I'm a player, I got all these girls or I'm doing all this and that's not what I'm trying to promote, you know what I'm saying?
It's just that the fact that I really
How true was what we were bearing witness to?
Chris, how true was that?
Are you in love with 2 people at the same time?
I guess when you feel it, you know it.
I think it's not something I can sit there and be like, I'm an expert on this and you can do it because guess what, you just do this.
It's a touchy situation.
It's difficult.
At the end of the day, I mean, I'm comfortable with talking about it towards you because it's family, but as far as the world goes and everything else, I'm not asking them to accept that.
Buy an album, dammit.
You want to hear some love for Nagle, some whatever, buy that carpe diem.
Buy whatever it is that you want to hear me say because I'm saying it on this
Did Carucci think why you didn't call me as opposed to putting out a video?
Oh yeah, of course.
But when you do that, you have to do it for yourself.
You can't do it for everybody else's feelings, and I love them to death, but it's just that at that time I needed to be out there because I can't just be like, hey, this is how I feel, because then he's like, what?
You have to at least let it be known and they can only accept you for being honest.
Chris Brown, I want you to fill in the blanks.
I look better than blank and I dance better than blank.
You look better than Dang, you have some very cocky questions.
All your artists are here.
All the artists probably just say, yeah, I look better than this dude.
I can't tell you how many times people say, man, I look better than They say Chris Brown all the time.
Well, that's gangsta.
I look better than I did yesterday and I dance better than
Wow.
I don't want to say the same
I dance better than Big Boy.
Wow.
We have a talent.
I know I'm lying.
You know you smoking, bro.
Plus, he seen my knee brace.
He trying to take advantage of me.
He know I'm on his little knee brace right now.
All right.
That's cool, bro.
Best believe that, man.
All right.
This is it.
Okay.
Gold, silver, bronze.
All right.
Chris Brown or Marion Usher?
Who's gold?
I'm Diamond.
Sorry.
Whose song is that?
I'm not taking away from them.
I just try to strive to be the best.
Maybe Rihanna's song.
I just try to strive for perfection.
Every time he see Rihanna's name, his eyes rolling.
And he starts stuttering.
Every time he like that.
He just starts stuttering every time.
So you're a diamond.
Shine bright like a diamond.
Yeah, I strive to be diamond.
I wouldn't say I am diamond.
I just try to be great.
Well, you know what?
That's good there, grasshopper.
Grasshopper.
I'm titanium.
Okay.
There it is.
You know what I mean?
Best believe that.
You ever seen when I take my chest out and I throw it in the 5th row?
Your chest?
You take your actual chest.
And throw it in the 5th row?
I gotta see that.
Are you doing that?
No, I'm trying to learn.
Exactly, exactly.
Best believe that.
Get on his level.
Yeah, man.
You got a long way to go there, diamond boy.
How's the basketball going for you, Chris Brown?
You still out there?
Yeah, man, I'm trying.
You know, I'm not trying to, you know, try out for any teams.
Right, right.
I just like it.
It's one of my fun leisure time activities.
All my friends do it.
I do it every time I'm on tour, on the road.
I try to do it and not get hurt before I get on stage.
They say J. Cole is pretty good.
He's not seeing me.
He knows it.
J. Cole's the homie.
Can you outball J. Cole?
Yes, he knows it.
Ask him.
When you get him on the show, ask him what happened.
We did.
That's why I'm asking you.
What did he say?
He said, you ain't nothing.
You can't see him.
I said y'all Instagraming.
I mean, instigating.
That's the new one.
Y'all Instagraming.
See, you trying to start mess.
You always trying to Instagram something, man.
J. Cole
If you and Game were to play right now just one on one, who wins?
Y'all stick around y'all radios we got Chris Brown in the neighborhood big boy