Everyone says that mastering Fortnite competitive takes multiple years and countless hours.
But what if I told you that I think I found a way to perfect Fortnite in a fraction of that?
Okay, okay.
I know that sounds crazy, but hear me out.
What if I trained like no other for 3 whole days leading up to the biggest tournament of the entire season?
Would pushing me far past my limit let me master Fortnite in such a short time?
Well, you'll have to watch to the end to find that out.
Starting off with day one, I went into Kovacs to train my aim.
Because honestly, I don't even think I could hit Jay Boolin with now.
After this, I went into Raider's mechanics training to warm up my fingers.
Because soon, me and my duo were gonna play some scrims.
So I needed to be completely dialed in so we could get some good practice.
Now it's time for our first scrim, where we dropped at our spot, got our medal, and were completely stacked for the end game, where this happened.
Okay, okay, I actually have no clue how I managed to die here, but my duo actually ended up clutching up a top 3 here, which seemed amazing, but it really wasn't.
Just let me explain.
You see, getting a top 3 was amazing, but I died before even reaching the top 10.
So that top 3 was really just my duo carrying me.
And if I'm supposed to master Fortnite competitive, I can't be getting carried.
After this, we played a couple more scrims.
Then we finished off the day by VOD reviewing every single game that we played to fix all of our mistakes.
See, usually now I'd be telling you what we did in day 2, but actually I didn't even get on for day 2.
Let me explain.
I was working at my job when my girlfriend texted me that her tire popped and I needed to come get her.
but when I got there to change her tire, it literally would not come off.
So of course we had to call roadside assistance and tell me why these people literally never showed up.
So when I got home super late, I was just tired.
So I went to bed, but now it's day 3, which is also the day of the tournament.
And I was already worried that I completely missed a day of my training.
But then of course my duo had to say this, bro,
I just lost power.
This was the worst scenario because I had no clue when his power was going to get back on.
But when he finally told me his power was back on, it was already an hour into the tournament.
I asked myself if we would even be able to qualify after starting an hour late since we needed a whole two hundred and sixty points to qualify.
But nonetheless, we landed into game one looking for an absolute bomb of a game to get us back on track.
right i'm dead dead these cracked 126126
Track 1 21.
I just died.
Hello.
Like, bro, are we serious?
I just died so it couldn't let me build, bro.
It seems great that you're dead.
The other kid has a chug jug.
The other kid is so bad, though.
That's so I don't know, bro.
It didn't let me build.
Like, I like I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing.
healing.
I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I'm healing, I
Okay, okay, I know what you're thinking.
How did you die to fall damage?
And honestly, I have no answer for that.
But we were still in terrible lobbies, so can't we just run it back?
Okay, clearly not, but maybe game 4 will be different because we decided to switch our place out to be more placement heavy.
have a boney.
You're good, you're good.
I'm going around.
Wrapping around.
Don't get beat don't get cracked I just got maxed
we're like a oh my how did you like actually good shot you have to third party dead
Oh, that's a man.
It's good to do right.
It's
Fuck it.
Let's see.
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry.
Cracked, cracked, cracked.
We're both under here.
All of us are under health.
Dropping it.
Disconnected it.
51 white.
That's a fucking bitch.
They're trying to fight.
They're fighting.
90.
Breeze, bro.
Like are we serious top13 try to get some top ten Why you just didn't crouch walk around Jetpack jetpack They're gonna
Okay an 11th place here is not that bad and shot us up a decent amount on the leaderboard.
Hopefully we can keep the momentum up going into game 5 where we start off with a mid game fight.
i just got maxed you and these come back
After this fight we went back in zone to get stacked again, but then we saw some bots that we thought we could get a lurk on.
After getting this refresh, we rotated one more time and when we landed, my duo made maybe the best call ever.
Told you this was the last refresh we needed to get us absolutely Stacked going into the end game where we were actually able to take height But little did we know keeping height would ruin our game.
Just watch.
We are in We are in Pretty I need hearts I got hella bad open that Watch out from it's you not landing on us
Bro, are we serious?
Where'd they jump from?
Where do they come from?
Drop, drop, drop.
You have 7 builds.
Hello, bro.
Get that, get that, you have to get that.
Thurbs, thurbs.
if you want to do the thing but you don't have to never mind no reason you're good that's a solo that gets so bad crack get the finish on the side never mind
You're on your side, on your side, nevermind.
That's a blue beacon.
On your side, on your side, behind you, behind you!
Puff high, you're good.
After this, our spirits were actually pretty high.
Until we died off spawn in game 6, making us need 2 wins to qualify for division 3, which is totally doable, right?
Right?
Yeah, I'm going to be so honest.
We dutted our last 4 games, finishing us with one hundred and sixty points, landing us in division 4.
Clearly, mastering competitive Fortnite was not that easy.
Hopefully in my next video, I'll be, you know, qualifying out of division 4 with all the scrubs.