How's it going all floor gang today we're checking out another TLC 90 Day fiance couple the fact that this is even a thing blows my mind It's so funny.
We've been through the Ed and Rose, but now we're checking out Colt and Larissa
My name is Colt.
I'm 33 years old.
I live in Las Vegas, Nevada and I dress up my cats See the thing about Colt is I don't think I've seen him erase his voice or get upset a single time in this Oh, you look so beautiful
I work as a software engineer and I live with my cats.
Baby girl.
God damn, that's a creepy cat.
What the hell?
That's terrifying.
He's just chilling in the closet.
The thing about Colt is that he lives with his mom and he's over 30 years old.
I definitely spoil Colt by doing everything around the house.
I don't think he even knows how to make a bed.
She's saying that that's like a good thing.
You clearly haven't taught him to take care of himself.
We'll get into it.
We'll get into all of the nuances.
Oh my god guys, it's crazy.
I thought maybe I could search outside the country, maybe find a girl and then I met Larissa.
Larissa lives in Brazil and she's 31 years old.
Can't find a girl in your country?
Then find a girl online.
Cringe.
Who would do that?
I had sent Larissa a message and to my surprise she actually responded and we started talking.
It wasn't long before I decided I really wanted to meet her in person.
So we worked it out and decided to meet in Cancun, Mexico.
When I got to the airport in Mexico, Larissa walked around the corner.
I saw her in, like, slow motion.
2 lovely shocks of her, Jesus.
She was the most beautiful woman I've ever seen.
I was like, I'm done.
This is it.
It was like all the boxes were checked.
She's beautiful, she's smart, and she seemed pretty cool with the idea.
And she's beautiful, she's smart, and I guess she's all right.
Living with my mother.
Oh!
after 5 days i knew spoiler she's not cool with it what girl likes the fact that they live with their mom that's the recipe for disaster i see my tambourine even picked this up himself pathetic the comments have no chill as always if this guy was a spice he would be flour
This guy has the personality of a butter sandwich.
This guy talks in lowercase.
Oh my god.
I love YouTube.
Leaving for the airport.
I decided to propose to her.
Why not?
Why not propose after you've just spent a vacation together?
That seems like a good reflection on how you you will get on for the rest of your life, please Don't marry someone before you at least live with them a little bit because that's a big adjustment to make it and you need that to work out for a marriage to work out Please stop cult cult Thank you Thank you, darling
Well, it's been a very long day, darling.
Honey, tell me, please.
Did you get it?
Not yet.
I think that you have to pick the next flight that you can.
We have no guarantee of the visa to arrive tomorrow or Monday.
I can't make a ticket to have the change fee and make another ticket.
You understand?
Yeah, that's pretty reasonable.
If you don't know when you're going to get the visa, you can't just keep rebooking the flight until you know.
No, baby.
What?
Oh, she's not happy.
I know you're disappointed, and I'm very sorry for that, but I did make plans.
What do you want me to do, cry?
You want me to roll up in a ball and cry?
Go to bed weeping?
Writing my diary and how sad I am?
But it's merely a week, probably less than a week.
We've been apart for a very long time.
Drama drama drama.
Okay, so she finally arrives where he lives in Las Vegas and a car with no air conditioning Which sounds awful Here we go
And, of course, she's not happy about it.
Oh, please.
Larissa has only been in Las Vegas for 3 hours, and she's literally not stopped complaining since she arrived here.
Larissa!
Where's my flowers?
You're so silly.
She's like, I'm not letting this go.
Where's my flowers?
Welcome to the desert there's nothing in Las Vegas unless you go to the strip I bet you had this image in your head that is gonna be amazing I get that she sounds very bratty but it's not that unreasonable to want flowers after a long flight first time you see each other she's coming over to live with him why am I defending her I don't know
I think Larissa and I will have some small hurdles to overcome initially.
I can't survive here.
Honey, I need you to stop, okay?
Just stop.
I need you to stop.
Stop talking.
Stop.
Stop!
Damn, the comments are on her side.
That's really interesting.
He hundred percent later on to think he was richer.
Larissa wanted a sugar daddy, but got a Splenda daddy.
What's a Splenda?
Oh, that's a artificial sweetener, isn't it?
Jesus Christ, that woman in the car is terrifying.
What the hell?
Ah, what was that?
I find a ghost.
Ah!
Stop.
So she meets with the mom Debbie.
So how was your trip?
The flight was amazing.
Yeah?
No turbulence.
So what do you think of Las Vegas?
OK.
What do you think of Las Vegas, honey?
No.
Las Vegas, I can't say the same about you.
it's not like the pictures it's not like the pictures i think she's a tiny bit disappointed yeah yeah a little bit but this is a beautiful house it's a beautiful house look we got the christmas things in the corner and we got the no sofa there's no sofa
yeah it looks like the mom decorated the entire house that's what that looks like oh god this is a recipe for a disaster i wanted to wait until you got here and now guess what you can pick one out yeah oh that's nice for me or all that's nice oh no she's crying oh no oh no oh she's happy for them okay great bro if i were her i'd be like okay back to brazil this
And it's ugly decoration.
I mean, she's not wrong.
It looks like an old man.
They court it.
I like the house.
But I think that we will move to a new house with.
You know.
She just came and she says we need to move no sensor no shell great.
This is great I can't so I would like to move to other house
I mean, I don't know what you want me to do.
You don't like Las Vegas.
You don't like the heat.
You don't like the house.
You don't like anything.
So I'm like, okay.
I mean, what do you want me to do?
This guy straight up picks her up in a bucket of a car with no flowers and brings back to mama's house.
My dad bought it for her.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
It's cute.
It's a toy.
It's nice.
You making dinner?
It's ready.
But you made it then.
Beef stew.
Let's go eat.
I can't watch this, it's too cringe.
Jesus Christ, dude.
Wait, she calls him Colty?
Colty.
I will move heaven and earth to make you happy, but sometimes your demands are quite ridiculous, honestly.
I just want to money.
Money, money, money, money.
She's so upfront.
Why don't we figure out a budget?
Jesus Christ.
Every month.
Prepaid credit card for you.
Just you.
Oh my God.
Perfect.
so what about it? uh, one thousand dollars? no, maybe in the middle, two hundred dollars.
Yes, let's go with that.
Damn, what a negotiator.
So, in a year, she can almost afford a Chanel bag if she saves all her money.
That seems like fair.
What's your annual income?
It's at two thousand dollars a year.
i think that's how i'm a good negotiator. i want one million dollars from colt. okay, you want one million dollars from colt. that'll take you just five hundred months. so in 4 to one years you'll get that 1000000.
So they go over to meet some of Colty's friends, and it goes great.
The day has finally come, huh.
Yeah,
Are you going to introduce me?
This is Larissa.
Hi, Larissa, how are you doing?
Welcome to America.
This is John.
You guys get along with living with each other and everything
We're doing pretty good.
It's not pretty. pretty good.
It's not good.
She has no filter.
Jesus Christ, dude,
Colt has. Wait, what?
Oh, no,
Encourage him,
And he thinks that show love is just
The reaction:
Yes,
Not just sex.
Hugging, kissing, being intimate, physically intimate. obviously,
Kolti has a great sexual drive.
Kolti wants to spend time together in the bed all day for his perfect.
And Kolti, I mean he's lived with his mom his entire life.
Of course Kolti is going to want to go bing, bong. you know what I mean.
I respect that, Kolti.
Fair enough,
You can always break this off.
The first time you could, you could always break this up in front of her. Jesus Christ. No, she'll, no one got no shield.
You could always break this up. You're not just coming over here to marry my man for a green card,
Are you?
The green card is nothing, just The, the rights to. I live here with him,
And he can take the divorce any time that he wants.
So it's not the guarantee,
It's a gamble, really.
I mean you want the high payoff.
You want to make sure your investment. you know, lose all your money right.
Welcome to Vegas,
You know, I think that she's coming to America to enjoy the you know high life,
The high
I don't know what her living situation in Brazil was. but I wouldn't call this the high life,
I wouldn't.
I don't want to be rude.
Also, for the record, no grown man should share a bank account with his mother.
Damn, people are simping for Larissa.
What the hell.
I did not expect this at all.
She's crazy.
They then have a barbecue. of course
It's great.
It's gonna go great.
Trust me,
She's all alone to make my life a hell like she does.
How is your life hell?
You have a man paying for you.
Your man pays for everything.
Your man pays for everything
Because you don't do a **** thing right now,
Jesus Christ.
And until you do and you understand respect,
Is she crying?
You're not acting.
This is great barbecue, guys.
This is a good time.
She's living the hot life, guys,
Come on.
When John says that he would like to take advantage of the coat, I just laugh,
Because advantage
What?
He's not a millionaire
Coat. having a cow is good.
No air conditioner.
So what kind of advantage are you taking
Using his body?
Maybe
He's the only advantage
Cold's body.
He has a bigger breast than mine.
I like it very much.
It's very nice.
I can't pretend anymore.
It's just, this is fake.
It's anymore,
Were you?
What do you mean?
Love is enduring for the other,
Love is fighting for the other
In my
Don't call me to my wedding. okay,
What do you think that you are?
Everyone that's against me.
You're fictitious,
Pretty successful barbecue,
I don't know about you, but I think that went great.
Yeah,
I expected Larissa to be the sweet, wonderful person that Colt told me so much about, but when she gets here, she's just not the same person.
Why am I laughing?
It's horrible, but it's so funny.
I don't know why
Bro Larissa's the man of the house.
I made a nice dupe for Larissa, but she just wanted to be by herself, and it really kind of upset me.
It's okay, mom.
Aw, don't cry, mom.
Come over here, mom,
She'll eat the stew.
Come on, mom.
See,
See what I mean.
He makes it seem like, oh, I can't leave my mom because I take care of her.
She's taking care of you.
The f*** are you talking about?
She cooks and cleans and everything.
I can't leave my mom.
I'm too young man,
So weird.
Moms are too attached to their sons.
I don't know.
It's not healthy.
I don't mean to call you guys out.
Eggo, you're farting,
Jesus Christ, dude,
I'm trying to record videos here.
You're making me all woozy.
So Larissa tries to take over the situation.
She's going to cook for Colty instead of mommy Debbie.
Oh, I don't know.
Eggs, bacon, ash browns-
I'm not a good cook. you know,
When I speak to Coach, I lie to him about my cooking skills, because I thought what do men like, sex and good food
Call your mother?
Colt doesn't usually eat bread for breakfast.
Colt doesn't eat bread for breakfast.
I'm his mother.
Lastly, I think that Colt is spoiled,
So it would be good if sometimes we make something simple.
He doesn't need to eat like a king in the morning.
So what do you want for breakfast tomorrow?
So she cooked for breakfast for him and the mom's like. so what do you want tomorrow? huh,
What the hell.
I'm worried about that. tomorrow, I guess
Ideally my mother could get along.
Yikes,
Oh God
The cringe.
She raised an extremely dependent son.
It's so unhealthy.
Water has more flavor than gold.
I spent 2 hours doing my makeup.
I took off the ring because I was upset.
What happened?
I feel sorry.
They're the dream couple.
How could this go wrong?
I just said to Cody, and he still wants to be Cody's wife.
So I hope, if I'm sweet. he can forgive me.
Hello,
How are you?
I'm fine.
I feel like Larissa and I are 2 different people.
We're basically polar opposites.
She goes from sweet to scary.
I decided to put the ring back.
That's nice.
What are you looking?
I'm looking at flights to Brazil.
Are you looking or are you trying to be here to me?
Look for yourself.
Oh, he's done.
I never thought that he'd be so.
man coach doesn't compliment me. a real man shouldn't act like this. it's really awkward and it's like: oh goodness, what do we do? spend 2 hours to get ready. she spent 2 hours. i know that you could. you won't say anything. it's not one time. 2 times, every time, you know, walk in my shoes. i work all day. i don't care. you're getting ready. that's a problem. you don't care. tired of you.
oh god, this is just funny. maybe it's you. you're crazy. you're crazy. i bet my life that every man will be loved to be by my side. i feel really embarrassed. right now, larissa has no right to start a fight with me in front of my friends in pub. oh god, how is this going to end? i don't know.
If Larissa doesn't apologize to my mother, I might have to make a very hard choice between a life with Larissa and a life with my mother.
My man just- ay, ay, ay.
My man just said that.
My man just said that unironically.
There it is.
I watched the video of the fight and the cousin started it. all called it a defender, so she had to do it herself.
Right,
You didn't defend her at all, you're right.
Damn, people hate the mom,
Debbie's so shady.
She tries to come up sweet like a victim, but she had such a bad vibe.
I feel like she's a minute- I don't-. I haven't seen any of this.
What are people picking up,
Debbie? I have something to say to you.
Oh,
You're pregnant,
I have a kid.
What
Did he know that?
You have children.
Colt's sitting there like a concerned teacher during a conference.
I'm sorry, his name is Colty.
Come on,
I need a drink.
I am shocked.
You haven't told me anything about it.
Did they divorce yet so he can finally marry his mother?
He has 0 percent masculinity.
Oh, my god.
Alright, that's the last clip.
That's the last clip.
That's all I know.
I don't know what happens next.
Why do I care about this?
It's funny.
I love this trash TV.
It's great.
Hope you guys enjoyed as well, subscribe. We're trying to beat Coco Mellon, become a member and catch the live streams, get early access to videos. a ton of benefits, Discord.
I really appreciate it's been really fun to build like a sub community on the channel. Thanks for doing that.
Appreciate all my floor game members and see you tomorrow.
Hey, Children of 9 parts. It's time to raise what was once forgotten.
Bot creatures, bot spells and poop troops await.
Poopty is coming to Nintendo Switch
And remember it has a very big pee-pee
Pre-order promotion, I mean.